Hey, everybody.
Happy Thanksgiving.
No, no, no.
Shh.
Are we keeping Thanksgiving
a secret this year?
No, we're playing this
game I learned at work.
You have to name
all the states
in six minutes.
What? That's like insanely easy.
No, it's a lot harder
than it sounds.
You always forget at least one,
or in some cases, fourteen.
It's a stupid game,
and I wasn't playing
against other people
so, technically,
I didn't lose.
You forgot 14 states?
Nobody cares
about the Dakotas.
( timer dinging )
Oop. Okay, time's up.
All right, I got 48.
That's not bad. Pheebs?
Well, I got tired
of naming states
so I decided to list
the types of celery.
And I have one-- regular celery.
Okay, so Rachel's got 48
and Phoebe has the lead
in... vegetables.
Joey?
Say hello to the new champ
of Chandler's dumb states game.
Wow, how many
do you got?
Fifty-six.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day,
your week, your month ♪
♪ Or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey, how is New England
not a state? Huh?
They have a sports team.
Does South Oregon
have a sports team?
There you go.
How come there's
one extra place setting?
Because you invited
your assistant.
Oh. Right. Sorry.
Tag's not coming.
His girlfriend
came into town
so he's spending
Thanksgiving with her.
Oh, why didn't you tell me?
I made him his own individual
sweet potato stuffed pumpkin.
Oh, well, I was going
to, but then I figured
you know, your food
is so delicious
and perfect
you can't ever have
too many of those
pumpkin things.
You'd think
I wouldn't enjoy that
because it is so fake,
but I still do.
Regular celery.
Oh, I already have that.
Oh...
Done... with time
to spare.
Ooh, this may be
a new world's record.
You know, I hate
to lecture you guys
but it's kind
of disgraceful
that a group
of well-educated adults
and Joey...
can't name all the states.
You ever see a map?
Or one of those round,
colorful things called a globe?
Hmm?
Uh, Magellan?
You got 46 states.
What?
That's impossible.
Forty-six.
Well, who's well educated now,
Mr. I-forgot-ten-states?
I'm out of oven space.
I'm going to go turn on Joey's.
Please watch him.
Do not let Joey eat
any of the food.
I am only one man.
( timer beeping )
Okay, Ross, time is up.
No, just give me
another minute.
Look, Ross, if you don't
know them by now
you will never know them, okay?
That is the beauty
of this game.
It makes you want
to kill yourself.
But th-th-this is crazy.
I can do this.
All right, uh, I bet
I can get all 50 before dinner.
Okay, but if you can't,
no dinner.
You're on.
All right.
Don't look at my list, Ross
'cause there's a lot on there
that you don't have.
Hey, did you guys know
that your oven doesn't work?
But the drawer full
of take-out menus
is okay, right?
Ross, I'm going
to use yours, okay?
Shh.
Chandler, give me a hand.
Sure. And, Joey,
do not let Ross look
at any of the maps
or the globe in your apartment.
Don't worry, Chandler.
It's not a globe of
the United States.
Hey, you guys, I'm going
to go out and take a walk.
Phoebe, why is
your bag moving?
Oh. It's not.
Seriously. It's moving.
What the hell's in there?
It's just my knitting,
that's all. Ooh.
Yes, I knit this.
I'm very good.
You know, Ross's
apartment is nice.
How come we don't hang out
here more often?
I don't know.
Maybe because it
smells so weird.
It's like old
pumpkins or something.
That's my pie.
Which smells delicious.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
What?
We left Joey alone
with the food.
Yep. Yep. I knew it.
There he is... feeding
stuffing to a dog!
( phone ringing )
Geller-Bing residence.
How can I help?
Phoebe, why is there
a dog in our apartment?
I'm sorry. Who's this?
Phoebe, there's a dog
sitting on my couch.
Tell her I am allergic,
and I will sue.
No, there's no dog here.
Yes, there is.
He's black and white
and shaggy
and he's sitting next to Rachel
and licking Rachel's hand.
Oh, my God, where are you?!
I'll be right there.
( knocking )
( gasping )
They're here already?
How are they doing this?!
Hi, Tag.
What are you doing here?
I, uh, wanted to see
if your offer
to spend Thanksgiving
with you was still good.
Well, sure. Come on in.
Well, what happened
to your girlfriend?
We, uh, kind of broke up
this morning.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, so she went
back to Ohio.
Ohio! Thank you.
Huh. Where's the dog?
What dog? There's no...
there's no dog here.
Yeah, that dog left.
Phoebe? Phoebe, open up.
Phoebe:
Th-there's no
dog in here.
( barking )
Phoebe, we can hear
the dog barking.
No, that's just
me coughing.
( forced coughing )
( barking )
Oh, good. There you are.
Listen, um, I have
a dog in my room.
What is it doing here?
Well, I'm watching it
for some friends who
went out of town.
Wait.
Hello. My name
is Clunkers.
May I please stay
with you nice people?
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
I wish you could stay here
but Chandler's allergic.
Extremely allergic, okay?
If I am anywhere near a dog
for more than five minutes
my throat will just close up.
That's odd, 'cause this
dog's been living here
for the past three days.
( hoarsely ):
Really?
Chandler, if the dog
has been here that long
and you haven't had
a reaction
maybe you're not allergic
to this dog.
Well, it still has to go, right?
Why?
Okay, it's, um...
Don't do it!
Don't do what?
I have to. Okay?
It's time.
Okay, I hate dogs.
What?
Are you out
of your mind?
Phoebe:
That's crazy. Why?
Told you.
They are needy.
They are jumpy.
And you can't tell
what they are thinking
and that scares me
a little bit.
You're right,
they are scary.
( screaming )
She just ate a treat
out of my hand!
Wait a minute.
Do you not like
all dogs?
I mean, not
even puppies?
Is there a puppy here?
You don't like puppies?
Okay, you are new.
Look, Chandler,
I told you.
Never tell anyone
about this dog thing.
It's like Ross
not liking ice cream.
You don't like ice cream?
It's too cold!
Okay, it's just that dogs
make me a little uncomfortable.
Hurts my teeth.
And I don't want to say this
and I don't want you guys
to hate me, but, uh...
I don't think I can be
around that dog anymore, okay?
So either the dog goes,
or I go. Huh.
Oh, my God!
How can I not get this?
I'm a college professor.
I got 1450 on my S.A.T.s.
1250.
Damn. I forgot you were here.
All right, we're going
to take Clunkers to Ross's.
We'll be back
in a minute.
Oh, wait. Before you guys go,
can I just ask you a question?
Yeah.
Um, when a guy breaks up
with his girlfriend
what is an appropriate amount
of time to wait
before you make a move?
Oh, I'd say
about a month.
Really? I'd say
three to four.
Half hour.
Interesting.
When it's your assistant,
I would say never.
Rach, the big question is,
does he like you? Right?
Because if he doesn't like you,
this is all a moo point.
Huh. A "moo" point?
Yeah. It's like
a cow's opinion.
You know, it just
doesn't matter.
It's moo.
Have I been living
with him for too long
or did that all
just make sense?
Please don't listen
to Joey.
Would you look at him?
He's obviously
depressed.
He's away from his family.
He's spending Thanksgiving
with strangers.
What he needs right now
is for you to be his friend.
Oh, you're right.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Okay, that's what
I'm going to do.
Fine. Take their advice.
No one ever listens to me.
When the package
is this pretty
no one cares what's inside.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Not bad.
Yeah? I'm sorry
about your girlfriend.
Thanks.
So were you guys together
a long time?
A year, on and off.
I kind of thought
we'd end up together.
I don't anymore.
Now that she
broke up with you?
Yeah.
Hmm...
It's weird. I always
used to assume
that I would
meet someone
and fall in love
and be happy
and that all that
was just a given.
But lately, it's like
what if it's not?
Do you ever have
that feeling?
No.
Yeah.
All the time. Constantly.
It's terrifying.
But you know, I figure,
it has to work out.
Why?
Because it has to.
You really have all
the answers, don't you?
Yeah. No, I do.
I really do.
Hey, thanks for
talking to me.
Come on, what are bosses for?
Hug it out.
All right, he
likes you back.
Huh? Told you
you should go for it.
What?
Street noise drown
any of that out?
No? All right,
I'll see you later. Okay.
What did Joey say?
I like you back?
Um, well, you... see...
Joey knows that I'm very...
insecure about my back
and... you were
hugging me
so obviously
you are not
repulsed by it.
Yeah!
Wait a minute.
That doesn't make any sense.
No?
All right.
Here's the truth.
Um... Joey said
what he said
because, um...
I'm attracted to you.
Wow.
Yeah, I admit it.
I have a crush on you
and, uh... and I know
that's crazy
because we work together
and nothing could
ever happen
and the last thing
I wanted to do
is to freak you out
or make you feel
uncomfortable.
Which is why it
would be really great
if you said something
right about now.
Oh, my God.
Those guys are
stealing my car.
What?
Right there!
That's my car!
Oh...
Hey!
Okay, well, that's
going to take one minute.
Do you have
anything else
you want to get
off your chest?
I can't believe this.
We still have time
to talk.
And they're not even
in the car yet.
Oh, look, there they go. Okay.
Okay, Phoebe, we should
probably go back now.
( high-pitched voice ):
Please don't leave me.
I'll be lonely.
Stop it.
Stop.
Okay, let's go.
We can be strong.
Yeah, okay.
( whimpering )
Oh, my God,
did you hear that?
She said "Monica!"
Oh, I can't leave her.
You know,
if you want
we could sneak the dog back in
and Chandler wouldn't even know.
That's not going to work.
I've had that
dog there
for three days
and Chandler had no idea.
He's not so smart...
Hey.
I didn't know either.
Yeah, but you kind of knew
that something was going on,
didn't you?
Yeah, I knew.
Where's Chandler?
Here I am.
Wash your hands!
How did you know?
Hey, what's she
doing back here?
Relax, Ross.
She's not made of ice cream.
Hey, look, Phoebe,
I laid out the states
geographically.
We don't really have time
for this right now.
We have to keep Chandler
away from my bedroom.
Yeah, but look
what I did...
See? This is exactly
what we do not have time for.
Where's Monica?
In Phoebe's room.
You can't go in there.
Why not?
( dog whimpering )
Monica's crying.
She's very upset
about this whole
Clunkers thing.
Well, I... I should
go in there.
No. No. No, she
doesn't want
to see you right now.
Why not?
Because you sent
away the dog.
That's ridiculous.
Oh, is it?
Is it?!
Look, when Monica
and I were kids
we had a dog named Rover
and, uh, one day my dad
decides he doesn't like dogs
so Monica and her
friend... Phyllis...
take away the dog
and that was the last time
we ever saw him.
Don't you see?
This is just like that
only with
a few details changed.
( door opens )
Okay, I'm in my sweatpants.
Bring on the food.
What's the matter?
Monica is all upset
because I sent Clunkers away.
So? Bring the dog back.
You're a hero.
Yeah, I can be a hero.
I could do that.
I could... I could do...
W-what if it attacks me?
Chandler, it's like
a big gerbil.
And that doesn't
scare you?
Ross, you need some help?
From you?
( chuckles, sobs )
( voice breaking ):
Yes, please.
First of all... Utah?
Dude, you can't just
make stuff up.
I hate America!
When I finish this game,
I swear I am moving.
Mmm.
Joey:
Hey.
Tag still talking
to the police?
Yeah. Oh, damn it!
Why did I open my mouth?
( whining ):
"I have a crush on you."
"I'm attracted to you."
I know that
I freaked him out.
If you said it like that,
you probably did, yeah.
Hey, is Chandler here?
Uh, no. No, he went for a walk.
Okay, well, you cannot tell him,
but look who's back!
( Rachel gasps )
Oh! Hi!
No, no, no,
no-no-no-no.
He went over to Ross's
to bring the dog
back here.
Oh, no! The dog's
not going to be there.
You think?
Hi, honey.
Please, please, please
don't be mad at me.
What? Wh-why would...
Shh. Wait and see.
Maybe we will,
maybe we won't.
Okay, I went over
to Ross's apartment
to bring back Clunkers,
you know
for you, and, uh,
I left the door open
and she must have...
gotten out
and I looked everywhere
all over the apartment,
including the roof
which, FYI, Ross,
one of your neighbors?
Growing weed.
I couldn't find him
and I am so, so, so sorry,
but... I do know
where we can all go
ease the pain.
We have good news.
Look who's back.
Hey!
Clunkers!
Oh, my God!
Monica:
That's right.
She came back
all by herself.
It's a Thanksgiving
miracle!
It is so good to see you!
Yeah, she came all the way
back from Ross's building.
Oh, the things
she must have seen!
And she climbed up
the fire escape
and she tapped on the window
with her teeny little paw
and then we ran
to let her in.
I went too far, didn't I?
When should I have stopped?
Okay, maybe
this is so hard
because there aren't 50 states.
Let me tell you something--
I had 49 states
and there are no more!
Now, I think I should
be able to eat something.
It's up to you.
( cries )
Oh, hi.
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
I got to go down
to the police station
and look at mug shots.
Thanks for having me
over, you guys.
Tag, you're going?
We didn't, uh...
We didn't even get
a chance to talk.
So, where did you say
you were from again?
Colorado.
Aw, what good are you?
Look, um, I think we
should talk about
what happened
on the terrace.
Okay.
Uh, I never should've
said what I said.
You know what, it just
doesn't matter how I feel.
We work together, so
nothing could really
ever happen between us.
And what I would love
is just to go
to work on Monday
and never talk
about this again.
Okay, big day Monday,
lots to do.
So, we okay?
Um, I'm not.
Oh, God, I knew it.
I freaked you out.
No, you didn't.
The only thing
that freaked me out
was you saying that nothing
could ever happen between us.
Really?
Yeah.
So please don't fire me
for doing this.
Okay, well,
that's one less thing
we have to do on Monday.
( knocking on door )
Delaware.
( cries ):
All right.
I want my turkey now.
You got it.
You got Nevada twice.
I know.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]